gogpayslip.com 2015-05-22

# Privacy Policy

**Introduction**   
It is the intent of www.gogpayslip.com and its affiliates and agents to comply in all material respects with all applicable privacy laws and, we are strongly committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This www.gogpayslip.com Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to information that is collected through the website located at www.gogpayslip.com ("Site"). Please carefully read this Policy before using the Site and providing any Information (defined below) through the Site. 

**User Consent to Privacy Policy**   
Any person accessing, browsing, or otherwise using this secure Site, either manually or via an automated device or program, shall be considered a "User." All Users are bound by the terms of this Policy. Users consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable User information and anonymous browsing information (collectively "Information") to the extent not prohibited by law. If you do not consent to this Policy, please do not access, browse, or use this Site. If you are more comfortable communicating with www.gogpayslip.com or CAGD offline about this service, feel free to contact us by mail or telephone using the contact information on the site before using the service. 

**User Information**   
User information that is collected are not different from what you already have with the CAGD. You can therefore browse the Site without revealing any other personally identifiable information, but anonymous browsing information may be collected. For example, our servers may collect anonymous browsing information, including your Internet Protocol address, your computer's operating system, the website you came from, and the name of the domain you used to access the system.

In order to provide these services, we collects a variety of personal information that already exist with CAGD, which may include, but is not limited to the following: staff ID, email address, telephone and fax numbers, credit card number, educational background, employer name, religious information and citizenship. 

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**   
We shall not disclose or share this information collected to any third party. 

**Linked Internet Websites**   
The Site may provide hyperlinks, which are highlighted words or pictures within a hypertext document that, when clicked, take you to another place within the document, to another document altogether, or may take you to a third party website not controlled by www.gogpayslip.com. These hyperlinked third party websites may collect, use and disclose Information different than this Site. www.gogpayslip.com is not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these web sites, and www.gogpayslip.com expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure. 

**Children**   
The Site is not directed towards children under 18 years of age and www.gogpayslip.com does not knowingly collect any information from children under 18 years of age through the Site. If you are under 18 years of age, you are not permitted to submit personal information to www.gogpayslip.com through the Site. 

**Security**   
This Site has security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Information under our control. Unfortunately, no system is perfect; therefore, www.gogpayslip.com makes no representations or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of these security measures. www.gogpayslip.com shall not be responsible for any actual or consequential damages that result from a lapse in compliance with this Policy because of a security breach or technical malfunction. 

**Applicable Law/International Issues**   
Information that is submitted to this Site will be collected, processed, stored, disclosed and disposed of in accordance with applicable GHANA law. If you are a non-GHANA User, you acknowledge and agree that www.gogpayslip.com may collect and use your Information, as discussed in this Policy, outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, such Information may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction. GHANA law may not provide the degree of protection for Information that is available in other countries. By providing www.gogpayslip.com with your Information, you acknowledge that you have read this Policy, understand it, agree to its terms and consent to the transfer of such Information outside your resident jurisdiction. If you do not consent to the terms of this Policy, please do not use this Site, but if you have already provided us with Information, please contact us at info@gogpayslip.com and let us know how you would like us to handle such information. 

**Amendments to Policy**   
www.gogpayslip.com reserves the right to amend this Policy periodically. Any amendments made to this Policy will be considered effective immediately after the amended Policy is posted on the Site. 

**Contact Information**   
If Users have any questions about our services, programs, the Site or this Policy, please contact info@gogpayslip.com
